今晚，在军法署...
Tonight, on JAG...
晚上好，我是诺曼·德拉波特
Good evening, I'm Norman Delaporte.
您将看到的报告
The report you are about to see
包含有关战争和死亡的详细描述
contains graphic descriptions of war and death.
涉及到关于战争罪行的突发新闻
It involves a breaking story about war crimes
由美国海军陆战队在沙漠风暴行动期间犯下
committed by American marines during Operation Desert Storm
在科威特的埃尔巴卡尔基地
here in Kuwait at the El Bakkar compound.
指控很严重；影响很大
The accusations are serious; The repercussions, great.
您正在观看的录像是由一支海军陆战队侦察小组拍摄的
The footage you are watching was shot by a marine force
他们在沙漠风暴地面战开始前一天被派往敌后
recon team sent behind enemy lines the day before
该小组由克莱德·莫里森中士领导
the ground-war phase of Desert Storm began.
消灭三名美国人
The team was led by Sergeant Clyde Morrison.
战争罪行是由当时的二等中尉弗兰科·切法鲁发现的
To eliminate three Americans.
两天前，我在弗吉尼亚北部的家中采访了弗兰科·切法鲁，
The war crime was discovered
现在是一名海军陆战队上尉
by then-second-Lieutenant Franco Cefalu.
我的部队在侦察部队突袭两天后占领了埃尔巴卡尔
Two days ago, I interviewed Franco Cefalu,
你在五号建筑里发现了什么？
now a marine captain, at his home in northern Virginia.
三名死去的美国人，
My unit overran El Bakkar two days after the Force Recon raid.
与萨达姆·侯赛因合作的化学工程师
And what did you find in building five?
参与他的制造大规模杀伤性武器的计划
Three dead Americans,
这三个人是怎么死的？
chemical engineers working with Saddam Hussein
死于沙林毒气的影响
on his program to develop weapons of mass destruction.
那晚拍摄的视频
How did these three men die?
显示侦察部队包围了五号建筑
From the effects of sarin gas.
遭到激烈抵抗，海军陆战队向建筑物发射了
Video footage shot that night
后来被证明是沙林毒气的罐子
shows the Force Recon team surrounding building five.
录像在莫里森中士的命令下停止了
Encountering fierce resistance, the marines fired canisters
停止！停下！停下来，离开这里！
of what later proved to be sarin gas into the building.
机密情报文件显示
That's when the taping stopped
美国军方知道这些工程师在埃尔巴卡尔的存在
at Sergeant Morrison's order.
五角大楼的一位高层消息人士证实，这些人
Stop! Stop it! Stop it and get out of here!
对我们的战争努力构成了严重威胁
Classified intelligence documents indicate
海军陆战队有四人伤亡
that the American military knew of the presence
幸存者被直升机空运出去
of these engineers at El Bakkar.
理查德·福特中士是机组长和炮手
A source high up in the Pentagon confirmed that these men
中士，你撤离的海军陆战队员
posed a serious threat to our war effort.
从埃尔巴卡尔带走了沙林毒气吗？
The marines suffered four casualties.
是的，先生，莫里森中士带走了，先生
The survivors were airlifted out by helicopter.
你怎么知道的？
Sergeant Richard Ford was crew chief and gunner.
他把它放在他的子弹带里，先生
Sergeant, did the marines you evacuated
我们将在一分钟后回来，带来五角大楼的反应
from El Bakkar carry sarin gas?
Yes, sir, Sergeant Morrison did, sir.
And how do you know that?
He had it in his bandolier, sir.
We'll be back in a minute with reaction from the Pentagon.
这些指控很严重...
The charges are serious...
美国人使用化学武器杀死其他美国人
Americans using chemical weapons to kill other Americans.
好吧，我会考虑行政解雇
Well, I'll consider an administrative discharge.
今天你最多能得到三年
Three's the best you're going to get today.
-几个月？ -几年
-Months? -Years.
你一定是在开玩笑
You've got to be kidding.
哈姆，埃尔斯沃斯下士偷了一辆推土机
Harm, Petty Officer Ellsworth stole
从一个保密设施里
a bulldozer from a secured facility
并摧毁了他当地国会议员的竞选总部
and destroyed the campaign headquarters
这是一种看法
of his local congressman.
我没有时间争论
That's one way of looking at it.
我得去接那个澳大利亚交流军官
I don't have time to argue.
布朗比少校
I've got to go pick up that Australian exchange officer
-让巴德去！ -我听说布朗比很帅